naturalcures.com 2016-05-10

# Privacy Policy | NaturalCures.com

Global Natural Cures LLC (NaturalCures.com) recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of all information provided by our users. We created the following policy guidelines with a fundamental respect for our users’ right to privacy to guide our relationships with our users.

  * The kinds of personal information we collect from users of the Site and how that information is collected;
  * How we use your personal information;
  * The circumstances under which we disclose personal information to third parties; and
  * The mechanisms we have implemented to protect your personal information.

We promise that we will take steps to use your personal information only in ways that are compatible with this Privacy Policy. The following policies are only to transactions made and data gathered on web pages, discussion lists and opt-in announcement lists owned and operated by Global Natural Cures LLC and does not apply to any other transactions, information, web site or Internet, telephone or offline point of contact between Global Natural Cures LLC and you or other consumers. As we continue to develop our Site and take advantage of technologies to improve the services we offer, this policy may change. Such revisions shall be effective to you immediately upon posting. We therefore encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy policy.

The terms and conditions of this Privacy are legally binding on all users. By using this web site, you consent to this Agreement and to the collection and use of information by Global Natural Cures LLC as specified below.

## What information are you collecting and how are you collecting it?

Every computer connected to the Internet is given a domain name and a set of numbers that serve as that computer’s “Internet Protocol” IP address. When a visitor requests a page from any Web site within the Global Natural Cures LLC Network, our Web servers automatically recognize that visitor’s domain name and IP address. The domain name and IP address reveal nothing personal about you other than the IP address from which you have accessed our site. We use this information to examine our traffic in aggregate, and to investigate misuse of the Global Natural Cures LLC Network, its users, or to cooperate with law enforcement. We do not collect and evaluate this information for specific individuals.

## What are cookies?

From time to time, Global Natural Cures LLC or its advertisers may send a “cookie” to your computer. A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. A cookie can’t read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other Web sites. Cookies do not damage your system. We use cookies to identify which areas of Global Natural Cures LLC’s Network of Web sites you have visited or customized, so the next time you visit, those pages may be readily accessible. Our advertisers may also use cookies to ascertain how many times you’ve seen an advertisement. Global Natural Cures LLC and/or our advertisers may use this information to better personalize the content, banners, and promotions that you see on our site. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your browser. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies, or allow your browser to show you when a cookie is being sent. If you choose not to accept these cookies, your experience at our Site and other Web sites may be diminished and some features may not work as intended.

## What information do you collect when I register for something?

Global Natural Cures LLC offers access to some services that are free but that require registration. We may use your registration contact information to send notification of Global Natural Cures LLC products and services by e-mail and/or postal mail. We may also use your IP address internally and share it with third parties for reporting and statistical purposes.

## What other information do you request?

We may also request your e-mail address or mailing address for the purposes of conducting a survey or to provide additional services (for example, subscriptions to e-mail newsletters, announcement lists or information about conferences and trade shows). Whenever we request the identity of a visitor, we will clearly indicate the purpose of the inquiry before the information is requested.

We may from time to time send e-mail announcing new Global Natural Cures LLC products and services. If you choose to supply your postal address in an online form, you may receive mailings from other third party companies.

When you enter a contest or other promotion, we may ask for your name, address, and e-mail address so we can administer the contest and notify winners.

## What information do you collect when I purchase something?

If you are purchasing something from Global Natural Cures LLC, we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card number and expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status. This information may also be used by us to notify you of related products and services.

We do not store personal or financial information in our database in the process of payment, nor do we share this information with 3rd parties.

Wherever Global Natural Cures LLC collects personal information we make an effort to include a link to this Privacy Policy on that page.

## Who do we share our information with?

**Companies That Help Deliver Global Natural Cures LLC  Products or Services**  
Sometimes we hire companies to help us deliver products or services (including processing your transaction, vendor direct shipping, credit card authorization and fraud prevention). In those instances, we need to share your information with these companies. Sometimes we also work with other companies who assist us in gathering your information in order to enable us and the other businesses of Global Natural Cures LLC to provide you products and services. All of these companies are only allowed to use your information for delivery of the product or service.

**Companies Offering Promotions, Products, or Services**  
On occasion, Global Natural Cures LLC may share your information with other unrelated outside third parties selected by us, so that these third parties can directly market their products or services via e-mail, telephone and/or postal mail.

**Information Sharing Between Affiliates**  
Global Natural Cures LLC reserves the right to share your personally identifiable information, including but not limited to your email, postal address, phone number and purchase history, with its Affiliates. Global Natural Cures LLC may share your personally identifiable information with Affiliates in order to conduct promotions, offer special premiums, and share databases and equipment. We reserve the right to share your information with other companies that become Affiliates.

**Third-Party Advertisers**  
Once you’ve clicked on a third-party advertisement and have left our Web site, our Privacy Policy no longer applies. You must read the privacy policy of the advertiser to see how your personal information will be handled on their site.

**Purchase or Sale of Businesses**  
As Global Natural Cures LLC continually strives to improve our business, from time to time, Global Natural Cures LLC may purchase a business or sell one or more of its businesses, and personally identifiable information regarding you may be transferred as a part of the purchase or sale. If Global Natural Cures LLC purchases a business, the personally identifiable information received with that business would be treated in accordance with the privacy policy of that business on the date of sale. If Global Natural Cures LLC and/or its units or subsidiaries are ever sold, acquired, merged, liquidated, reorganized, or otherwise transferred, we reserve the right to transfer our user databases together with any personally identifiable information contained therein, to a third-party. Global Natural Cures LLC will make reasonable efforts to include provisions in the selling contract to require the purchaser to treat your personally identifiable information in the same manner you requested under this Privacy Policy.

**Content Partners**  
On some of our sites, we provide content that is created by a third-party partner Web site. In some instances the third-party sites will collect information in order to facilitate the transaction or to make the use of their content more productive and efficient. In these circumstances the information collected is shared between Global Natural Cures LLC and our third-party sponsors. These third parties will receive your information because you will be visiting their Web sites or using their links and, in doing so, you may provide information directly to them. You therefore should refer to their privacy policies to understand how they handle your information and what kinds of choices you have.

On some of our sites, Global Natural Cures LLC may provide you with a link to the supplier of that product so that you may get further information. If you link to the supplier’s site, the supplier may collect or receive information about you.

You also may make a purchase from Global Natural Cures LLC through a link from another Web site or search engine and may use their express checkout tool to do so. When you do, please be aware that both Global Natural Cures LLC and that Web site or search engine will receive your information.

**Mandatory Disclosures Required By Law**  
Global Natural Cures LLC will disclose personal information and/or an IP address, when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to:

  1. Conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Global Natural Cures LLC,
  2. Protect and defend the rights or property of the Global Natural Cures LLC Network of sites and related properties, or visitors to the Global Natural Cures LLC Network of sites and related properties,
  3. Identify persons who may be violating the law, the Global Natural Cures LLC Terms of Use Agreement, the rights of third parties, or otherwise misusing the Global Natural Cures LLC Network or its related properties,
  4. Cooperate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities.

## Your Control Over Your Personal Information

**Opt-Out**  
Every communication Global Natural Cures LLC sends you will contain a clearly worded “Opt-Out” or “Unsubscribe” link allowing you to withdraw your permission for future mailings. Please allow five to seven days for processing. Permission changes will however not affect any information which you provided to us and which we previously shared with third parties and/or Content Partners.

## Other Matters

**Your California Privacy Rights**  
As of January 1, 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits visitors to this Site who are residents of California to request information regarding Global Natural Cures LLC’s disclosure of their information to third parties for direct marketing purposes.

**Data Security**  
Global Natural Cures LLC is committed to doing its best to maintain the security of information collected on our site.  
While no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure from intrusion, we have used and will continue to use commercially reasonable efforts to put in place the appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect. When you place orders for purchased products or access your payment information, we use industry standard SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption technology to protect the storage and transfer of your data from unauthorized parties. Encryption is a process by which a message or information is scrambled while it is in transit to our website SSL codes the information transferred between you and the server, rendering it unreadable to anyone trying to intercept the information. In addition to our online security efforts, we take steps to protect your personal data offline, as well. All sensitive information and/or systems that house that information (i.e., computers or filing cabinet) have physically restricted access in our offices. Employees are granted access on a need-to-know basis pursuant to specific job function requirements (for example, a billing clerk or a customer service representative). Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices through periodic training sessions in an effort to keep security awareness levels high.

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**  
Global Natural Cures LLC will occasionally update this Privacy Policy in response to changing business circumstances and legal developments. Global Natural Cures LLC encourages you to periodically review this Policy to be informed of how we are protecting your information.

**Information About Children**  
We are committed to protecting the privacy and rights of children online. We believe that children should be able to use the Internet in a safe, productive, and efficient manner and should be afforded the highest protection available with respect to their personal information. The Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”) took effect on April 21, 2000 and imposes certain requirements on Web sites directed toward children under 13 that collect information on those children, or on Web sites that know they are collecting information on children under the age of 13. It currently is Global Natural Cures LLC’s policy not to collect personal information on any person under 13. While we do no specifically seek to obtain information from children, there are areas of our website that children may visit. To learn more about COPPA, consult the Federal Trade Commission’s COPPA Web Site [www.ftc.gov](http://www.ftc.gov/) or you may call 202/FTC-HELP.

By using this web site, you consent to this Agreement and to the collection and use of information by Global Natural Cures LLC as specified above.

## Contact Details

**Company Address:**  Global Natural Cures LLC, 215 West Poplar, Rogers, Arkansas 72756, USA

**Customer Service Phone:** 1-888-923-8446 Monday – Friday 8AM – 8PM, Saturday 9AM – 3PM CST

**Customer Service Email:** [Support](http://naturalcures.com/contact-us/)
